快点儿
Come on.
快点儿  快点儿
Come on. Come on.
该死
Ow! Damn it.
每个一年级医学院学生都知道
Any first-year med student knows
心跳加速是不好的征兆
That an increased heart rate is a sign of trouble.
-整整一天都这样 -一整天都跟着斯蒂文斯混日子
-All day of this.-All day stuck with stevens.
我们干嘛非待在门诊室不可?
Why are we in the clinic?
-我们可是外科医生啊  -但今天不是
-I thought we were supposed to be surgeons.  -Not today we're not.
今天我们只能帮流感病人打针还有灌肠
Today is gonna be about flu shots and enemas.
真是太虚度年华了
What a colossal waste of time.
早
Morning.
心跳加速暗示了很多种可能
A racing heart could indicate anything...
也许是惊恐发作
From a panic disorder...
-老天  对不起  -不  应该我说对不起
-Oh god. Oh i'm sorry.-No   i'm sorry.
我  我什么都没看到  对不起
I uh no i uh  Didn't even look. I'm sorry.
-你在干嘛 -不用这样
-What--what are you -No   no   no.
我现在就走  我现在就走
I-i'll leave. I'll leave.
没关系  你睡会儿吧  你在这儿熬了一夜了
No. Sleep. You've been here all night.
你怎么知道我在这熬了一夜
Uh... How do you know that I've been here allnight?
也许是一些...
To something much...
我就是知道
Uh... I just knew it.
更加严重的情况
Much more serious.
你应该把头发挽起来
You should wear your hair up more.
这样能露出你美丽的后颈
It shows off the back of your neck.
我喜欢你的后颈
I like the back of your neck.
心跳加速
A heart that flutters...
或是心率不齐
Or one that skips a beat...
我以为你去睡觉了
Hey I thought you were sleeping.
没有  亨特在值班室
No. Hunt was in the on-call room.
-你和欧文亨特干"坏"事了?  -没有
-You had dirty sex with Owen Hunt?  -No. It's
一点都不坏  而且我们也没有嘿咻  我们只是...
It's not dirty and it's not sex. It's...
我也不知道那是什么
I don't know what it is.
-可能预示着内心隐秘的冲突 -嗨  最近怎样?
-Could be a sign of a secret affliction  -Hey how's it going?
老天  谢谢你的问候  我很好
Oh my god. Thank you for asking. It's great.
我是说  他真是个有趣的人
I mean he's fun and he's funny.
就算不做爱的时候  我们有时候就只是大笑
Even with no sex allowed I mean we--we just laugh
我们聊天
And we--we talk and--
-我不想听这些  -拜托  你得听听
-Yeah. I don't want to hear this.  -Come on. But you have to.
只有你知道我们的事情
It's just you're the only one who knows about us
而且我不善于保密
And--and i'm terrible at keeping secrets.
-保密这件事让我觉得很恶心 -听着 独身的人
-Keeping secrets makes me sick.  -Look alone people
不喜欢听情侣间的故事  懂吗
Don't like to hear about the together people  okay?
就算是自己选择独身的人
Even if the alone people are alone by choice
打个比方来说
It's--it's sort of mean.
这就像你带了半打啤酒去一个戒酒会
It's sort of like bringing a six-pack to an a.a. Meeting. But--
-但是这些酒你只能自己喝  -我是啊
-Keep it to yourself.  -I am.
帮我个忙  这是我妈妈的日记  第九本日记
Uh  i need a favor.My mother's journal her ninth journal--
-我想你帮我先看看  -为什么?
-I need you to pre-read it for me.  -Why?
我妈妈和主任有婚外情
My mother had an affair with the chief.
你妈妈和她的主任医师有婚外情? 爱丽丝真够牛
Your mother had an affair with her chief resident? Rock on Ellis.
不 不是她的主任  是我们的主任
No no no no no. Not her chief. Our chief.
如果读到那一段的话你恨不得自己瞎了
Oh  yeah. You'll go blind reading that.
这也可能隐匿着浪漫关系...
Or it could indicate romance...
这才是最大的麻烦
Which is the biggest trouble of all.
这是什么?
Whoa. What is that?
-你觉得这是什么  -这是危险品
What you think it is.That's dangerous.
带着枪的人更容易伤到自己
People who carry guns are more likely to fire 'em.
我准备好开这一枪了
Oh  i'm ready to fire it.
这不是问题之所在  但她是个问题
That's not the problem. She's the problem.
她很容易被吓到  所以我要找个适当的时机
She spooks easy. I have to fire at the right time
用适当的方法开这枪  否则她会被吓跑
In the right way   otherwise she'll panic and bolt.
她还没准备好  你觉得她准备好了吗 我不知道
She's not ready. Do you think she's ready? I don't know.
但是更重要的是  如果你不确定的话
More importantly if you don't know
还是啥都不做比较好  等你确定了再说 斯隆医生
You shouldn't do anything until you do know.Dr. Sloan.
亨特医生
Dr. Hunt.
我们速战速决吧
Oh  let's make this quick.
可以走了?
So we good to go?
嗯  行事聪明点儿
Yep.  Use it wisely.
今天我跟你
Hey. I'm with you today.
你跟马克·斯隆之间怎么了?
So   uh   what's going on with you and mark sloan?
什么? 没事啊  怎么了?
What? Nothing. Why? No  why  why?
你以为有什么?
What did you think is--was?
因为你跟他一起工作了一个多星期了
Well  because you've been on his service for over a week.
你知道的  我真的对整形外科很感兴趣
you know i'm--i'm really interested in plastics
这个...这个专业  我真的很喜欢
A-as a--as a specialty.  I'm fascinated.
我...我很喜欢人脸
I-i like f-faces.
车祸引起的钝伤
Vehicular blunt trauma
右肩受伤  在现场暂时控制了伤势
Right shoulder.  Stabilized in the field.
帮帮我们  拜托了!
Somebody help us   please!
-珍  亲爱的  -慢慢来 求求你救救我的丈夫
-Jen   honey -Slow down, will you?
-我开车撞倒了他  -亲爱的  亲爱的...
-I ran him over with the car.  -Sweetie   sweetie...
-你冷静一点  -我知道
-You have to calm down.  -Okay.
-我不会有事的  -好的  我很冷静
-I'm gonna be fine. I'm gonna be fine.  -Okay i'm calm.
-我很冷静  我很冷静  -没事的 会没事的...
-I'm calm. I'm calm.  -Okay. All right.  It's gonna be--
老天  是我脑子不好  因为怀孕脑子变笨了
Oh my god it's my brain. It's my stupid pregnant brain.
我开车的时候不小心  亲爱的  对不起
I left the car in drive. Oh god baby. I'm so sorry.
这只是个常规的神经检查
It's a normal neuro exam.
他的肩关节错位了
Okay well he's got an inferior shoulder dislocation
还伴有一些软组织断裂  他需要手术
And some associated fractures.He'll definitely need surgery.
手术的时候  斯隆会帮他割掉腐肉
Sloan will debride the burns when he's in surgery.
-手术?  -宝贝  -她的血压是170/100
-Surgery?  -Oh baby.  -Her b.p. Is 170 over 100.
-给她注射5毫升肼苯哒嗪  -老天
-Give her 5 of hydralazine.  -Oh my god.
-亲爱的 冷静下来 宝宝怎么样? -一直在乱踢我
-Sweetie just calm down.  How's the baby?  -Kicking like crazy
-正在挤压我的膀胱 -乐观点
-And pressing right on my bladder.   -Well look on the bright side.
-至少她没有开辆卡车来撞你  -谢谢
At least uh she's not running you over with a truck.  -Thank you.
你想要辆SUV对吗
Hey you wanted the s.u.v. right?
是妊娠高压综合症对吧 没错  我要在胎儿受到影响之前
Pregnancy-induced hypertension?
想办法把她血压降下来
Before it starts affecting the baby.
多恩爱的夫妻  他们会生出可爱的孩子的
Oh nice couple. They'll have cute kids.
是啊  但不会有我们的孩子可爱...
Yeah not as cute as ours...
但仍然算是可爱的
But cute.
怎么了?
What?
没什么
Nothing.
已经三天了  三天的假期
It's been three days--three days of vacation--
除去我休产假外
The only three days I've ever taken
我就休息了这三天而已
Other than my maternity leave.
-我知道我的进度有点落后了 但是  -贝利 我懂你的意思
Now I know I'm behind but  -Bailey I get it.
杰克逊 普里斯科特的病情不好处理
Jackson prescott was not an easy case.
-我不会怪你的  -老实说  主任
I don't begrudge you that.Okay frankly sir
我希望不要再接那些垂死的孩子的病例了
I would rather not work on another dying kid again.
但你不用担心知道吗  我会跟上进度的
But no need to worry  okay?  I-i will catch up
-我会  -我不担心
-And i'll  -I'm not worrying.
我想提拔你
I'm promoting you.
我想在普通外科多加一个主治医生
I need another attending in general surgery.
我向董事会提交了申请  我推选了你
I'm submitting to the board, that it be you
今年七月你完成了住院医生实习期后
And that it starts this july
就可以正式上任了
The minute you've completed your residency.
我知道背后有人议论说
Now i know there was some talk a while back
你已经厌倦了阑尾炎和胆囊炎手术
About you getting tired of appys and gall bladders...
没有  满满一板的阑尾炎和胆囊炎手术
No  a f-full roster of appys and gall bladders...
听起来很带劲的  主任
Sounds just perfect  sir.
好吧好吧  但今天不要做这些了
All right  all right. But not today  though.
狄克逊要你去协助她
Dixon's requested you on her service.
这件事还是得看董事会是否同意  贝利
This is subject to Board approval  Bailey
不过我觉得没什么问题
Though i'm not worried.
你现在没话说了吗
You have less to say now   huh?
出去吧
Get outta here.
狄克逊医生不喜欢跟人有目光接触
Dr. Dixon is not big on eye contact
所以如果她老是不看你别觉得奇怪
So don't be surprised if she doesn't look at you.
还要避免肢体接触
Also try to avoid physical contact
-不要发出噪音吵到她  -她是正常人吧?
Uh  loud or disruptive noises-She's okay  right?
-她医术好吗  -她相当出色
She's a good doctor? Oh no she's amazing.
你找不到比她更好的外科医生了
You couldn't ask for a better surgeon.
我只是想让你有个心理准备
I'm only telling you so you'll be better prepared.
狄克逊医生  贝利医生  这是丹·普洛克和他太太丽莎
Dr. Dixon  dr. Bailey  this is Uh Dan and Lisa Pollock.
我想看看病人  病人在哪儿?
I need to see the patient.  Where's the patient?
在这儿
Uh  right this way.
这是史黛西·普洛克  9岁
this is Stacy Pollock  age 9.
她患有继发性肺动脉高压症
She's suffering from secondary pulmonary hypertension
是由室间隔缺损引起的
Due to a v.s.d.
心电图显示她的左心室肥大
Her e.k.g. Also shows  um  a left ventricular hypertrophy
还有她的右...
Also evidence of right...
需要帮忙吗
Hi. Can i help you folks?
他不行
Not him.
有什么问题吗
What's the trouble?
-他也不行  -谢谢你  我们再等等
-Not him  either.  -Oh  uh  thank you.  We'll wait.
他怎么样?  你好  抱歉打扰你了
What about him? H-hello.  Yes i'm sorry.
请问你能帮帮我们吗  我就想...
Could you help us  please?  I would just--
-我们需要跟一个成熟点的医生谈谈 -他是这里的外科主任
-We need to talk to a grown-up.  -This is the chief of surgery.
没关系  克莱夫医生
No just hold on Dr. Karev.
我同样也是一个医生  你们需要什么帮助?
That doesn't mean i'm not a doctor. How can we help?
-我和我丈夫  我们  -我们的孩子去上大学了
Uh  my husband and i  we Our children went off to college.
一个在斯坦福  一个在西亚图华盛顿大学
One's at stanford. The other's at uh u-dub.
所以呢?
Yeah?
我们尝试了一种新东西
We tried something
一种全新的  然后
A new thing and...
滑的东西  我们把它丢在了
Something slipped And we lost this--
瑞吉儿
Rachel
我们从杂志上读到
We were reading this thing
这个方法
In a magazine
对  就在这里
Oh   here.
20种方法重燃
"20 techniques
你的漫漫长夜
To reignite your nights“
我们做了第九种
We did number nine.
额  你先换上病服  然后
Um... Let's get you in a gown so
不是我  是他  他照做了第九种
No   him  He did number nine.
是我们一起做的
We did number nine.
是这样  但我可没把它
Yeah   i'm not the one with it
卡在我的
Stuck inside my--
是他  他才是病人
It's him. He's the patient.
先请坐吧
Have a seat
我们会帮你搞定的
And we'll take care of you.
额  我想我还是站着吧
Um... I'll... I'll stand.
你现在就要给他做手术吗
You're taking him now for surgery?
是的  现在是最好时机
Yeah   it's a good thing.
我们能把他脱臼的地方接上
We can get his dislocation fixed
这样就能防止
So we can prevent problems
他的循环系统出现问题
With his circulation.
她最近一次血压还是在102到162间
Her last b.p. was still up 162 over 102
是啊  妇产科医生在担心
Okay  well  The o.b. was worried
她胎盘的供血量
About placental blood flow.
看着她  让她保持冷静
Stay with her and  just try to
-知道吗  -好的
-keep her calm  okay?  -Okay
-奶酪汉堡  -噢
-Cheeseburgers  -Oh
看来止痛片起作用了
Painkillers are working.Is there
还有什么需要帮忙的吗
anything else that i can get you
我没事  你确定现在就要
Um   i'm okay. Just--are you
-带走他吗  -是的
-Really taking him now?  -Yeah
奶酪汉堡
Mmm. Cheeseburgers.
Cheeseburgers.
她在吃东西的时候
She's   um   more relaxed
会比较放松
When she eats.
奶酪汉堡能使她平静
Cheeseburgers calm her down.
谢谢提醒
Thanks for the tip.
斯泰西有先天性房室间隔缺损
Stacy has a v.s.d.
病情在不断恶化
Which has gotten worse over time and
并且引发了肺动脉高压
has created Pulmonary hypertension
就是说她要动手术?
Does that mean she needs surgery
-是的  -你还好吗
-Yes.  -You okay?
如果那孩子真像看上去那样
If that child so much as looks
快要死的话
Like she's going to die
我就立刻走出去
I'm walking out of here.
我将会实施
I'll be performing a
经导管封堵手术
transcatheter closure
来修复隔膜内的损伤
To repair the defect in the septum
那孩子完全听不懂她在说什么
That baby doesn't understand a
所有的开胸手术
word she's saying  All open-heart
都有一定风险
Procedures have certain risks
嗨  她只是在说
She was just saying that we're
我们会修好你用来输血给肺的
gonna fix the part of your heart
那部分心脏
that pumps the blood to your lungs
那是轻而易举的事情
It should be a simple patch repair
就像那种很容易就修好的东西
Uh probably something easy to fix.
但我们必须切开胸骨的全长
But a full midline sternotomy
你看  她现在正在安排一切
Okay  now she's just making stuff up
护士会拿给你签写表格
The nurses have some forms For you to sign
哇  你的袜子真漂亮
Oh   i like your socks.
谢谢  这是足球袜
Thanks.  They're for soccer.
我是我们队里踢得最好的
I'm the best on my team.
妈妈总说我吹牛
Mom says it's bragging.
但爸爸相信我  因为这是真的
Dad says it's not  It's just the truth
你无法抗拒真实的自己
You can't fight who you are.
因为你是最好的  你是最好的
If you're the best  You're the best.
等你治好我的心脏
When you fix my heart
我还要多久才能
How soon will i be able
踢球
To play soccer again?
我已经错过半个赛季了
I missed half the season already.
这  我们还要
Well... Um   we'll...
等些时候
Have to... See.
克里斯蒂娜
Ah   cristina.
你跟她说了戒指的事么
Did you tell her about the ring?
噢  我可不想谈论你那
Oh   i don't want to talk
-愚蠢的戒指  -很好  千万别说
-About your stupid ring  -Good Don't
噢  你该不会要扮演罗曼蒂克的
Oh   you're not gonna do a big thing
美梦先生之类的吧
Like some big  romantic MCDREAMY
她可不喜欢那种东西
Thing?are you? 'Cause she'd hate that.
可是她用蜡烛围起座房子
Well   she built a house of candles.
那是为了你  她为你用蜡烛
Yeah   for you. She built you
围起间房子
A house of candles...
因为你喜欢那种东西
'Cause you like that sort of thing.
-她可不喜欢  -知道了  谢谢
-She doesn't.  -Okay   thanks.
日记看得怎么样
How is it? The journal.
语言粗俗吗  他们都脱光了吗
Is it gross?  Were they naked?
不  还没
No   not yet.
确实有一点
It's kind of   um...
热辣  但更像是是纯洁的热辣
hot actually  But like chastely hot.
全是什么暗送秋波
It's all stolen glances
眉目传情之类的
And loaded exchanges.
读起来就像维多利亚时期的
The thing reads like A victorian
-浪漫主义小说  -噢  很好
-romance novel.  -Oh  that's good.
纯洁是很好的事
Chaste is good.
他们一旦做了我会告诉你的
I'll let you know when they do it.
加里·巴拉德医生
Dr. Gary ballard
请前来服务台
Please report to the information desk
她说了关于孩子的话
She said a thing about babies--
就好像孩子是个
You know like babies were
很普通的话题
A totally ordinary idea.
她不害怕了  她准备好了
She's not afraid. She's ready.
-你准备什么时候开口  -说什么
-When are you gonna do it? -Do what?
-谢博德要求婚了  -真的吗
-Shepherd's proposing.  -No kidding?
-真是太棒了  -是啊  谢谢
-Outstanding.  -Yeah   thank you.
你准备怎么求婚
Uh   h-how are you gonna do it?
还没想好  我才刚决定
I don't know. I just decided.
-早上好  先生  -谢博德要求婚了
-Morning. Sir  -Shepherd's proposing
恭喜你 你迈出了很大一步
Congratulations.That's a big step.
多谢
Thank you very much.
你想让人尽皆知么
You just gonna tell everybody now?
你需要建议
You need advice.
亨特  你以前求过婚吗
Hunt You ever propose before?
很抱歉  我没这份幸运
Uh   sorry.  I'm not the guy to ask.
你准备什么时候说
When are you gonna do it?
重要的是
Well   more importantly
我要怎么做
How am i gonna do it?
你要用什么
So what do you use
一把麻花钻
Like a twist drill for that?
噢  不  如果你不想来个
Uh   no   not if you don't want
部分颅骨血肿的话
A partial parietal hematoma.
嘿  祝你好运
Hey. Good luck.
别逢人就说好吗
Just don't tell anybody else  okay?
我可是信任你的
I thought i could trust you.
你当然能相信我
Of course you can trust me.
这病例可是让我们
We got the short end of the stick
-开了眼界  -别笑了
-with this case.  -Quit laughing.
我们会笑晕的
We're gonna get reamed.
伙计们  病人可看得见你们
Dudes   the patient can see you
像八卦少女一样在这里偷笑
Giggling over here like schoolgirls.
再笑小心嘴裂开
Enough wisecracks.
裂开
Cracks.
有什么这么好笑
What's so funny?
对不起  先生  这帮白痴
Sorry   sir.   These idiots
在这里无聊
Were screwing around
我正教训他们呢
And i kinda got   uh...sucked into it
够了
Enough.
如果你们这些小子
Now if you children need
需要上下职业操守课的话
A lesson in professionalism
好好看着我是怎么做的
Then come and see how it's done.
克莱默先生
Mr. Kramer.
你的腹部双侧X光片
Your biplane abdominal Radiographs
显示里面有异物
Show a foreign body.
我们将为你进行乙状结肠镜检查
We will perform a sigmoidoscopy
然后人工取出异物
And then proceed with manual extraction
你们能拿出它
You'll get it out?
对  我们会拿出它的
Oh   we'll get it out.
-再坚持下  -这已经是第三次了
-Just hold it  -That is the third time
-出什么问题了  -我知道  我
-What's the problem?  -I know. I--
她找不到静脉
She can't find a vein
她把我当成个
And she's poking me
刺绣品一样在戳
Like i'm her needlepoint.
天啊  你们这些家伙到底在做什么
Look  what is wrong with you people?
你们没互相间联系过吗
Didn't you practice this on each other?
看着
Look...
好吧  当你找到根合适的静脉
All right  When you have a good vein
像这根一样  饱满而有弹性
It should feel bouncy like this one.
好了  现在找个角度插入
Okay   now go in at an angle
不是90度
Not at 90 degrees.
对  像这样
Yeah. Yeah   like that.
很好
Good.
接着让她给您注射
Next time  She'll do it on you.
你不如  自己一口气
You know what    Why don't you
都做了吧
run them both?
听着  伙计们
Listen up   you guys.
你们今天再做任何操作前
Before you run any more procedures
都先让我看看
today  Come see me first.
亨特说你那东西的没什么大问题了
So... Clean bill of health from hunt.
那么你又能重新上"马"了
You gonna get back on the horse then?
我不想用"马"这个字  不过
Well  i wouldn't use the word "horse"
不交往了  没结果的
but no. That's not gonna work out.
计划有变  我想
Things have changed.I think i'm
我不得不跟她分手了
going to have to break up with her.
什么  你出什么毛病了  为什么
You're what? What is wrong with you? Why...
抱歉  我刚去确认
Sorry. I had to make sure
病人妻子的情况是否稳定
The patient's wife is stable.
她血压偏高  我觉得这手术
She's hypertensive and i think
对她的压力
this surgery's more stressful on her
比对她丈夫还大
Than it is on him.
该死  这里有个大裂口
Damn it.There's a huge tear.
他锁骨骨折后
His clavicle fracture is
插进了动脉里
Jutting into the artery.
格蕾  握住止血钳
Grey   hold this clamp
我来  我来稳住血压
I got this.  I'll hold pressure.
呼叫亨特  让他快来
Page hunt.  Get him in here now.
情况不妙  病人不稳定了
No they can't  The patient's unstable
他锁下动脉正出血
His subclavian`s bleeding out .
他们正呼叫亨特医生
They're paging dr. Hunt.
-情况看起来不妙  -好的  谢谢
-It doesn`t look good  -Okay thanks.
噢  他们怎么说
Oh   what'd they say?
进展顺利还是
Did they say it's going well or--
手术时间将比预期的
It's  it's taking a little longer than
要长些
Than expected.
好的
Okay.
但  别担心
But d-don't--don't worry
因为一切都进展顺利
Because it--it's going great.
进展顺利  是吗
It is. Are you sure?
是的
Yes   it--you know...
他们不慌不忙说明一切正常
It's good when they take their time.
现在我们还没任何
You know right now
理由去怀疑
there is no reason to believe that
他会重新好起来
that he's not gonna be Just fine.
好的  多谢
Okay. Oh   thank you.
你的血压在降低
Hey   your pressure is way down.
珍
Jen?
怎么了
What's happening?
她的血管堵塞  血压骤降
She's tamponading Her b.p's crashed
而且心音模糊
And she has Muffled heart sounds.
该死  手套
Oh damn it. Okay gloves.
杨  用聚烯吡酮碘  看看情况
Yang Betadine and get a local.
史黛西  宝贝儿  你会没事的  好吗
Stacy sweetie you're gonna be all right okay?
别担心  18单位
Don't worry. 18-guage.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
丽莎  你应该出去
Okay Lisa you're gonna want to  uh  turn around or leave.
你不会想看这个
You're not gonna want to watch this.
杨   保持渗出部位的超声
Yang   keep the ultrasound Over the effusion.
是  能看到
Yeah I got it.
史黛西  亲爱的  你会感觉到有一点点被掐疼的感觉
Stacy  honey  you're gonna feel a little pinch
然后有很大的压迫感...
And then a lot of pressure...
然后你就会好很多  好吗
And then you're gonna be all better   okay?
开始啦
Here we go.
好的  做得好  史黛西
Good. Oh  good job  Stacy.
看到没  好起来了
Yeah see?It's all better.
很好  做得好  亲爱的
Good job.Good job   honey.
好多了
All better.
她的肺内压力很高
Her pulmonary pressures are high.
你是对的  她有肺心病
You're right.She's got cor pulmonale.
我在把她的手术提前  杨正在准备手术室
I'm moving up her surgery.Yang's getting an o.r. Now.
手术室见  贝利医生
I'll see you in there Dr. Bailey.
-告诉我情况 -干得好  贝利医生
-Let me know how it goes.-Great save dr. Bailey
我想你最好留下来
I think you better stay.
我不参加这个手术
I'm not scrubbing in on this one.
贝利  你能胜任这个手术
Bailey... You can handle this surgery.
是  我能胜任
Yeah I can handle the surgery.
我不能胜任的是看着另一个孩子
What I can't handle is feeling another child
在我面前死去
Slipping away right in front of me.
大部分情况下他们都不会死  甚至是那些病危的孩子
Mostly they don't slip away even the really sick ones.
杰克森是个例外但  但他都活了下来
Jackson was a special case and--and even he survived.
死里逃生
By the skin of his teeth.
但他活了下来
But he survived.
孩子们充满了活力  生命有无限的可能性
Children are resilient And in all likelihood
你将要打开这孩子的胸腔
You're gonna open up this girl's chest
把一些简单的东西修复好
And fix something simple
然后把她剩下的人生
And then you're gonna hand her back
交给她自己
The rest of her life.
告诉你  贝利  你会为了这个留下来
I'm telling you  bailey  You want to be there for that.
拜托  拜托  稳定下来
Come on  come on  come on.Stabilize.
血压在回升
B.p.'s going up.
正在回升
Going up.
谢谢你
Thank you.
恩  可以出院了
Yep. Should be good to go.
格蕾医生  珍·哈蒙
Dr. Grey jen harmon--
告诉珍  他稳定下来了
Tell jen he's stable.
-她不好了  她癫痫发作  -癫痫?
-She's not.She had a seizure.-A seizure?
这里有我们  格蕾  去帮她
We got him  grey.Go help her.
你是个白痴
You're an idiot.
啥
Excuse me?
你是个白痴  你有啥毛病吧
You're an idiot.What is your problem?
他要向她求婚
He is proposing to her.
她就变成了他的小妹妹
That makes little her his little sister
我可不能再跟他的哪个妹妹上床了
And I can't sleep with any more of his sisters.
而且她这么年轻  我还是她上司
And she's young and i'm her boss.
-我还是独身主义者呢  -那些跟这有什么关系
-And I'm celibate.-What does that have to do with anything?
单身是寂寞的
Celibacy is lonely.
别把时间浪费在想你是什么
Don't spend all your time wondering what you are
或者  或者你喜欢谁或者哪个适合你
Or--or--or who you like or whether it's right for you
还是不适合你
Or wrong for you.
只是让你自己开心点好吗
Just let yourself be happy   okay?
在你发现自己是一个人
Before you find yourself alone
是单身以前
And celibate.
她真的要做胸射线检查吗
Does she really need a chest x-ray?
她得了流感
She's got the flu.
也有可能是急性肺炎
Say that after You've ruled out pneumonia.
快点  有效率点
And be quick and efficient.
面带微笑
Keep a smile on your face
做点又蠢又开心的对话
And make stupid happy small talk
分散他们的注意力  让他们别那么紧张
To keep them distracted and...not panicky.
好吧  现在我要跟你谈谈吗
Okay. Should I do small talk now?
别  叫我躺着别动  深呼吸
No. Just tell me to lie still and take a deep breath.
好  深吸一口气
Okay   big breath in...
别动
And then don't move.
厄  那--那你准备怎么做
So  uh  uh  how--How are you gonna do it?
你准备  恩  做一个隆重而浪漫的求婚动作吗
Are you gonna  uh  go big a grand  romantic gesture?
额  我--我还不知道呢  主任
Um... I-- don't know yet   chief.
我不确定梅瑞狄斯是喜欢隆重求婚的那型女孩
I'm not sure that meredith's a grand gesture kinda girl.
噢  那你是想搞隆重的那种
Oh  you want to do the grand gesture.
这可是你婚姻的基调
It's the opening pitch of your marriage.
可以决定你的婚姻
It can determine the entire game.
你得全力以赴
You gotta go all out.
你的计划里要包括花  蜡烛
Now your plan should include flowers  candles
美味的食物  现场的音乐还有划艇
Exotic foods  live musicians and rowboat.
叫个飞机喷雾写字都不为过
Skywriting is not out of the question.
-现在你得  -谢博德医生
-Now you gotta go-- -Dr. Shepherd.
-在  -他归你了  归你了
-Yes.-Uh  uh  you got him.You got him.
好
Okay.
-你好  -怎么了
-Hi -What's up?
我需要一个神经科的会诊
I need a neuro consult.
-好的  -对  当然  你得走了
-Okay. -Yeah that's bet--You know you better go.
谢谢主任  好了
Thanks chief. Okay.
好耶  好耶
Okay   okay.
你还好吗  克莱默先生
How are we doing Mr. Kramer?
很不错
Oh fantastic.
很好
Good.
他们没合上"还能指望什么"这书
They didn't cover this In the "what to expect" books.
他们没说  "有癫痫"
They didn't say"expect seizures."
我知道  所以我们才要做这个检查  好吗
I know. That's why we're going to do an exam   okay?
-现在我想要你看着下面  -好的
-Now i need you to look down for me.-Okay.
喔  那是什么
Ooh   what is that?
什么  噢 恩  格蕾医生
What? Oh. Um   Dr. Grey.
你能  能给哈蒙太太预定一个核磁共振吗
Could you uh set up an m.r.i. For mrs. Harmon
-马上可以吗  -但你看见了--
-Please right now?-But did you see--
现在  格蕾医生
Now Dr. Grey.
好的
Okay.
噢  你  你看到什么啦
Oh  you--you saw something?
不  不  不  对不起
No   no   no. No   i'm sorry.
很好  你能帮我保守秘密吗
All right.can you keep a secret?
我打赌我能
I bet i can.
这是给格雷的
This is intended For Dr. Grey.
应该是个惊喜
It's supposed to be a surprise.
天哪  我几乎把事情搞砸了
-Oh my god.And i almost blew it.  -Yeah.
你准备今天送吗
When are you gonna do it today?
今天送了吧
Oh please do it today.
在这做好让我能看见
Do it here so i can see.
不  我不知道  不
No. I-i don't know. No.
有人说应该弄个仪式什么的
I was told it's supposed to be like a grand gesture.
罗布是在一个超市通道里向我求婚的
Oh well rob proposed to me in a supermarket aisle.
他说那是
He said that was the place
我们第一次见面的地方
he saw me for the first time.
所以我在猫食和卫生棉条中间答应了他
So i said yes between the cat food and the tampons.
噢  那很浪漫
Oh. That's romantic.
确实是的
It was actually.
我们还是得做磁共振吧
We still have to do the m.r.i.Okay?
保险起见
Just to be safe.
没问题  谢博特医生
Okay. Dr. Shepherd.
是的
Yes.
我应该害怕吗
Should i be scared?
不  那我呢?
No. Should i?
不
No.
-艾森曼格复合病  -能治吗
-Eisenmenger's complex.  -Can it be repaired?
这  没办法挽救吗
Is it--Is it too far gone?
孩子年轻的肌体还很有弹性
Children are resilient young.
你十次有九次觉得容易治
Nine times out of ten you find something simple to fix...
什么意思
What is it?
我能治疗室间膜缺损
I can repair the v.s.d.
不过这颗心脏已经不行了
But this heart is finished.
在我见过的里面
This is one of the most diseased hearts
这是最糟糕的之一
I've ever seen.
体外膜肺氧也许能支撑她一下
Ecmo might hold her over
不过没有心脏移植的话
But without a heart-lung transplant
她就会死
She's going to die.
贝利医生  贝利医生
Dr. Bailey?Um dr. Bailey?
没问题狄克逊医生  我能缝合好这些
It's okay dr. Dixon.I can take care of these sutures.
还有她的心
Her heart,is too
有太多疤痕组织要修补
There's far too much scar tissue to repair.
我们已经给她的静脉注射了药物
We have started her on i.v. Medications
她需要持续的用药
Which she will need on a continuous basis.
要多久呢  多久她...
For how long?How long does she--
到她可以接受移植
Until she can receive a transplant.
不过...要几个月吗
But... months?
也许几年
Years  possibly.
几年吗  她会躺几年吗
Years? S'll lay in a bed for years?
恐怕是这样
I'm afraid so yes.
贝利医生去哪了
Where's dr. Bailey gone?
你需要做一个切片检查
You want to take narrow slices with the scan
就能有一个更全面的了解
So you get a more comprehensive look.
你看到了什么
What do you see?
我看到...
Uh i see...
一个疯子
A crazy person.
无理由的做昂贵的测试
Taking expensive tests for no reason.
噢我看到老大正在找
And oh i see the chief finding out
然后把这个疯子弄出去  然后
And expelling the crazy person And then   uh
我看到  没工作  没了家  和沮丧
I see uh joblessness homelessness and depression.
没错  伊兹看起来不好
Yeah  It does not look good izzie.
看起来不好
It doesn't look good.
有人在外面敲欧麦利医生的门
Somebody kick dr. O'malley out of the booth.
嗨  你看到贝利了吗
Hey   have you seen bailey?
不过我得告诉你  德里克疯了
No but i have to talk to you.Derek is going crazy.
早上我说了些关于生宝宝的事
This morning i said something about having cute babies
那以后她变得很奇怪还躲着我
And now ever since he's been acting weird and avoiding me
我一走近他就不讲话
And dropping conversations when i walk up.
我说他是想要孩子了  他一直想要
I mean he wants babies.He's always wanted babies.
他是想要孩子
Oh   he wants babies.
也许他只是不想要我的孩子
Maybe he just doesn't want my babies.
不  不是那样
No that--that's not it.
因为我的孩子将来会得老年痴呆
Yeah  because my babies will have alzheimer's
还会有自杀倾向
And suicidal tendencies
还有头发分叉
And split ends.
没错  可能有你的原因
Yeah  you might have something there.
不  我真的不认为有你的原因
No   I really don't think you do though.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是珍
I'm jen.
进度怎样了?
How we doing?
都好了吗
We all set?
如果  如果你要马上做的话
If--if you're gonna do it do it soon.
她真的会被吓坏的
She's really freaking out.
谢谢
Thank you.
他们试了9号吗
They tried number nine?
谁是9号
Who does nine?
我个人是5号的粉丝
Personally I'm a fan of five...
7号  8号...
Seven   eight...
没错  12号几乎穿过20号
Well  Pretty much 12 through 20.
我会试试15号
I would try 15.
别试15号  别试
Don't try 15.Don't try 15.
我试试16号
I would try 16.
好的  我以前也没那样做过
Yeah. I've never done that before.
你试了16号吗
You'd try 16?
我会  我肯定会的
Mm-hmm. I would.I totally would.
16号别做太快  也许你...会伤的很重...
Um  don't do 16 too fast.It can--you get hurt... Badly...
我听到了
I've heard.
你们知道谁像那个优秀的12号吗
Do you know who likes a good 12?
嗨  你今晚要值班吗
Hey   you on call tonight?
貌似如此  你呢
Looks like it. You?
你说如果她不用
And you're saying if she misses
哪怕一剂药
Even one dose of her medicine
-会很麻烦吗  -是致命的
-That would be bad?-It would be fatal.
那些药
The drug
每三秒就要做一次
Needs to be administered at 3-minute intervals.
你的意思就是她得在医院躺很多年
So she'll live in a hospital bed for years you said.
不  不  有别的办法
No   no  there's another way.
有个办法可以让她不用这样
There's a way she won't have to stay in the bed.
做一个肺静脉血压的诊断
With a diagnosis of pulmonary hypertension--
这姑娘需要个背包  不  不
Ane girl needs a backpack.No   no--
一个背包  带便携泵的
A backpack--It has a portable pump
那会给她输送药物让她可以玩
That will deliver her meds and allow her to play
还可以上学
And go to school.
她能有个快乐的童年直到有新心脏
She can have a childhood until she gets her new heart.
这些
This is something
我们事先应该私下谈谈吧
That we should have discussed privately earlier--
然后她就可以离开医院吗
And she could leave the hospital?
是的  可以  她得一直背着那背包
Yes  she can.See she has to wear the backpack at all times.
我们会有教你怎样操作的程序
We will put you in a program teach you how to administer
这药  你有更好的吗
The medications--Do you have a prettier one?
天哪  贝利医生  谢谢你
Oh   my god  dr. Bailey . Thank you.
狄克逊医生  太感谢你了
Dr. Dixon thank you so much.
太感谢你了  狄克逊医生...
Thank you so much.Dr. Dixon...
谢谢
Oh--Thank you.
不  不  不不...
No... No No No...
狄克逊医生
Oh   uh... Dr. Dixon.
我能做点什么吗  帮的上什么忙吗
What--what can i do?how can i help?
你可以看看草案然后我可以选择
You can observe protocol and i was getting to that option
不过它太多了  只是太
But it was too much.It was just too--
太多叫喊  太多接触
Too much yelling Too much touching
太多
Too much...
好的  然后让你静一静好...
Okay  um... Then i'll leave you alone to uh--
不  不  我不要一个人呆
No   no.I don't need alone.
我需要压力
I need pressure.
我想让我的神经系统镇定点
I need my nervous system suppressed.
我需要持久的  深的...
I need constant   deep...
高压
Tight pressure
穿过我大部分身体
Across large areas of my body.
我需要你抱住我
I need you to hold me.
好的
Oh. Okay. Um--
紧点  紧一点  紧紧地
Tight. Tight.Tight. Tightly.
再抱紧点儿
Tighter.
你力气太小了
You're a very tiny person.
我需要一个力气比你  比你大的人
I need a bigger per-- person than you.
我是不是应该...
Should I...
我...我能帮上什么吗
Oh... what-- what can I do?
来这边儿  抱住狄克逊医生
Uh...get over here, and hug on dr. Dixon.
还是打一针氯丙嗪(镇静剂)好了
I was thinking more like a shot of thorazine.
快过来
Get over here.
过来
Yeah. Come.
抱住...
H--just...
好的
Yeah. Good.
动脉瘤
An aneurysm?
脑动脉瘤
A brain aneurysm?
你的症状
All of your symptoms--
健忘 头晕  慢性头痛
Forgetfulness, dizziness, chronic headaches--
都可能与怀孕有关
can all be associated with pregnancy.
但我们认为  你出现这些症状
The only reason we discovered yours
只是因为发病
because of the seizure.
你是说  你能治好我吗
So what   you said you can-- you can fix it?
你能把肿瘤取出来吗
You can take it out?
只要罗伯的术后并发症情况好转
We'll do it first thing in the morning
我们即刻给你
after Rob's recovered from the complications
动手术
with his surgery.
并发症  什么意思
Complications? Wait, what?
你们说过  说过没事的  你们说过他没事的
You said--you said it was fine. You said he was okay.
你们骗我
You lied to me?
抱歉  我只是
I'm-- I'm sorry. I just--
在我搞清状况前不想让你担心  他现在很好
I didn't want to worry you until I knew and he's fine.
你也很快就没事了
And you'll be fine, too.
但不排除有意外对不对
But it could burst, right?
珍 你得冷静下来
Jen... you have to stay calm.
你刚宣布我的脑袋里有颗定时炸弹
You just told me there's a time bomb in my head.
告诉你我没法儿冷静
I promise you that I'm not gonna stay calm.
牛在被宰杀之前
Cows are squeezed tightly in a chute
待在一个很窄的槽里
before they're slaughtered.
槽产生的极大压力
The chute applies intense pressure
使牛的脉搏率  代谢率下降
resulting in decreased pulse rate... metabolic rate
牛肉鲜嫩
and muscle tone.
压力能让它们镇定
It calms them down.
这也适用于和我有同样毛病的人
The same principles apply to people like me.
拥抱机用于
A hugging machine is used
放松交感神经系统
to relax the sympathetic nervous system.
减缓心跳
It slows the heart.
很好  挺有效的
This is good. Th-- It's working.
-那我们能歇会了  -不行
Oh...so we can stop now?- No.
马上就好了  克莱默先生
Almost there, mr. Kramer.
坚持
Hold on.
-好了  -天哪
- There. Got it.- Oh... my god.
谢谢
Oh... thank you.
再也不想玩刺激的了
Never again will I try to spice things up.
不找刺激了
I'm not spicing anything up.
你们有点超过了
Well...you tried to step it up.
第五条之前的都值得一试
Anything above number five deserves props.
听起来你好像感觉不错
Sounds to me like you're doing pretty good.
你们俩在一起  都竭尽全力地
You're together... you're both bending over backwards
寻求新方式来满足对方
to find new ways to... make each other happy.
如果稍微保守一点的话
You take a step back
你会发现其实恰到好处
You'll realize that you're doing just fine.
"竭尽全力"
"bending over backwards."
你们能放开我了
You can let me go now.
抱歉
Oh... sorry.
斯蒂文斯医生  血液测试结果出来了
Dr. Stevens, I have the blood test results.
怎么样
What is it?
你有贫血的症状
Well... you're anemic. Um--
贫血
Anemic?
幸好
Oh... my god.
你知道你刚才做了什么吗
Do you realize what you just did?
你的表情说的是我快死了
Your face said that I was going to die
不是我该补补了
not "go get a hamburger."
我...
Well... see... I- I-
控制你的表情 也是护理病人的一方面
That's part of patient care controlling your face.
-我只想  -贫血
- I- I just w- - Anemic.
没关系
This is fine.
没什么大不了  根本不算什么
This is no big deal. It's like nothing.
那位女士  她叫什么名字
How's mrs. What's-her-name?
很麻烦  对不对
That's not good, is it?
对
Yeah. No. Um...
她体内的乳酸脱氢酶值太高了
Her l.d.h. is off the charts.
那是什么意思  癌症吗
Oh, what is it?Is it--is it cancer?
参照肿瘤学
Consult oncology.
检查病情
Start a workup.
别担心  我们一起和她说
It's okay. We'll tell her together.
谢谢
Thank you.
我不想保密
I don't want to keep secrets.
你说什么
Sorry?
一整天我都没说实话
I've been keeping secrets all day.
关于手术的事  戒指  还有  你
A- about surgeries, and rings and-- and you.
那个秘密  你的秘密
And-- and that secret, the-- the-- the you secret
血压都升高了
It's giving me high blood pressure.
我不想再保密了
And I- I don't want that secret.
我们俩正在...
We're having...
谈恋爱
a relationship.
如果我们真的  在恋爱
And if we are, if we're in a relationship
那我希望  我们能让姐姐
Then I need to be in it in front of my sister
和德里克·谢博德都知道这件事
and Derek Shepherd.
如果不能让他们知道
If we can't do that
那我们还是算了
then I can't do this.
戴维斯医生  创伤救护组去加护病房  三楼东
Dr. Davis, trauma team to i.c.u. On three east.
怎么啦
What's going on?
抱歉  出什么事了
Sorry. What happened?
你在发抖
You're shaking.
抱歉  我做不到  请你出去
I'm sorry. I can't. Just leave-- leave me alone.
我...看见了认识的人  应付不来
I... Saw someone-- someone I knew. I can't do this.
-我做不到  -没事
-I can't. Just...- Okay.
请你离开
Please go away.
没关系的  没事的
Okay. It's-- it's all right. Here. It's okay.
不  我不要这样
No,no. I don't want this. Okay.
不用了  不用了
- I don't want this.I don't want it.
我现在给你极大的压力
Okay, I'm applying deep pressure here...
-现在不行  -放松放松
-I can't do this now - To relax-- to relax
你的交感神经系统
your sympathetic nervous system.
能降低你身体的代谢率
It'll decrease your metabolic rate.
一开始你会更慌张
You will feel more panicked at first.
不要这样
I don't want this.
你一定行的
You'll try to resist it.
但最终你的脉搏率会降低
But eventually you will feel your pulse rate slow.
你的脉搏率降低了  没事了  没事了
You'll feel your pulse rate slow. It's okay. It's okay.
-呼吸顺畅了  -不用了...
-Your breath will come easier. - I don't...
呼吸顺畅了
Your breath will come easier.
抱歉  我失控了
I'm sorry for my outburst.
应该先告诉你的
I should've spoken to you first.
也许说的不合适
It was inappropriate
但我以为小儿外科医生
but I've come to expect it from pediatric surgeons
总是不按规矩办事
always breaking protocol.
但我不是小儿外科医生
But I'm not a pediatric surgeon.
最近是在儿科的做了几个手术
I've landed a few peds surg cases recently
不过马上就回普通外科了
but I'm getting back to general surgery.
我得到的第一个机会
The first chance I get.
每次你和这孩子说话  都会摸摸她
You touch the child whenever you speak with her
在给家长解释病情的同时 也没忽略孩子
You explain conditions to the child not just the parents
把病人当成自己的孩子一样对待
and you react to the patient as if it was your own child
不按规矩办事是不合适
and you break protocol which is inappropriate
除了在小儿外科
except in the case of pediatric surgery
只有那儿的规章比较"灵活"
Where protocols are constantly evolving.
你不是普外科医生
You are not a general surgeon.
你是儿科医生
You're a pediatric surgeon.
吃了吗
Hey. um Did you eat?
我换件衣服  我们一起走
Let me change. I'll come with you.
不不  不行  我  我得工作
No, no, no. I can't. I've...I have to,um... work.
好吧  听着  自从我跟你说了宝宝的事
Okay, listen. You have been acting like a basket case ever since
你就一直举止异常
I dropped that stupid little comment about babies.
我很高兴我说了
And I'm glad I dropped it
如果你不想要宝宝
Because if you don't babies
或是不想宝宝继承我的弱智血统
or you don't want babies with me and my crappy D.N.A.
尽管说
just say so.
不用躲着我
You don't have to avoid me
也不用拿工作来搪塞我
And you don't have to make up lame excuses about work.
梅瑞狄斯  我喜欢你的弱智宝宝
Meredith, I want your crappy babies.
-是吗  -生几个都行
- You do?  - All of 'em.
那好  去吃饭吧
Okay. Do you want to eat?
不  我真的  得去工作
No. I-I have...I gotta... I have to work.
我的天
Oh, my god.
你把她的背包打满了亮片
Did you use a bedazzler?
便携亮片机  电视里推荐的
Circa 1986. As seen on tv.
狄克逊说得没错
Dixon's right, you know?
你的确适合儿科工作
You do belong in peds surgery.
我的孩子去年差点死去
My own baby almost died last year.
医院里的医生们  朋友们
The doctors in this hospital... my friends...
他们拼尽全力抢救他
They all worked to save his life.
我站在手术室外
And I stood outside the room
觉得自己  毫无用处
Feeling so... useless
六神无主  孤单无助
So pointless and helpless
就好像  天要塌了
Like... I was losing everything in the world.
他被抢救过来后
And when he didn't die
我发誓绝不再体验
See, I knew I didn't want to be anywhere near
这种感受
that feeling again.
经过那件事
So I think that makes me
我很不适合儿科手术
pretty unsuitable for pediatric surgery.
我觉得
I'd say...
你因此更适合了
That makes you uniquely qualified.
我能坐这儿吗
You mind if I sit here?
可以  我只是想得太多了
No, no. I'm just... overthinking.
你觉得他会告诉他吗
You think he'll tell him?
除非他傻
If he's not an idiot.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我没
I don't...
我很好
I'm fine.
德里克他
Derek is a...
你们干什么呢
What are you doing?
不知道  只是
I don't know. I just...
在这呆会儿
I'm just staying here.
好吧  晚安
Okay. Good night.
他打算求婚
Uh, he's planning to propose.
什么
Wh-what?
主任
The chief.
你母亲写道  他说打算离开埃德勒
Your mother writes he, uh told her he would leave Adele
回来向她单膝跪地求婚
And come back and get on one knee and propose
貌似最后没有发生
But... I don't think he ever did.
真伤感
That's sad.
伤感吗
Is it?
也挺浪漫的
Or romantic.
看来  我们根本无法控制
It seems we have no control whatsoever...
自己的心
Over our own hearts.
矫形科的是吗
Ortho, right?
-是的  -你好
- Yeah, right. - Hi.
我是爱利桑那 洛宾斯  在儿科工作
I'm Arizona Robbins. Peds surgery.
在医院见过你
I've seen you at the hospital.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事  我很好
Yeah, no. I'm fine. I'm... fine.
我们那的人喜欢八卦
People talk. Where we work, they talk...
很八卦
A lot.
为了表示诚意
So for the sake of being honest
我该告诉你  我知道你的事
I-I think I should tell you that I know things about you
因为他们八卦
Because people talk.
你是指
You mean...
好极了
Terrific.
说对了
It is, actually...
被八卦是好事儿
The talk.
那里的人都喜欢你
People really like you over there.
他们尊敬你
They...they respect you
关心你  对你的事好奇
And they're concerned and interested.
他们真的喜欢你
They really like you.
个别人
Some of them...
真的"喜欢"你
Really like you.
你看上去不开心
You just...you look upset.
你也应该知道
And I...and I thought that you should know
八卦是好事儿
That the talk is good.
当你走出困境  当你
And when you're not upset when you're over...
不再沮丧
Being upset...
会发现喜欢你的人络绎不绝
There will be people lining up for you.
能报几个名字出来吗
You want to give me some names?
身边的世界瞬息万变
Conditions can change without warning.
你知道了
I think you'll know.
浪漫让人心动不已
Romance can make the heart pound...
而恐惧
Just like panic can...
真是蠢
This is stupid.
她绝不会喜欢的
She's gonna hate this.
这些花吗  哪个女孩不爱花
What, the flowers? girls love this crap.
太土了  我真是土鳖
It's a cliche? I'm a cliche?
土办法之所以成为土办法
Cliche became cliche for a reason.
是因为有实效
Because they worked.
心情异常激动  不是吗
It's great, isn't it
你对她怀有强烈的感情  而且
When you feel so strongly for someone, and it's...
不只是为了性
It's not just about the sex?
而是
It is...
真情
It's true.
你不该说这种话
You should not talk like that.
好吧  我不说了
Yeah, you're right.
准备妥当了  剩下的交给你了
Well, you're all set here. I'm gonna leave you to it.
多谢
Thanks.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
谢谢
Thanks.
恐惧
And panic...
爱狄森
Addison?
能让澎湃的心绪嘎然而止
Can make it stop cold in your chest.
发生什么了
What happened?
难怪医生们哪怕费时费力
It's no wonder doctors spend so much time
也要保持平稳的心率
Trying to keep the heart stable...
让心脏慢慢地跳动
To keep it slow...
平稳地跳动
Steady...
规则地跳动
Regular...
不让心从喉咙口跳出来
To stop the heart from pounding out of your chest...
避免受坏消息惊吓
From the dread of something terrible...
避免满心期望
Or the anticipation...
等来一场空
Of something else entirely.